Richmond Beteise

Web Developer | Mobile App Developer | Al Enthusiast | Embedded System developer

■ beteiserichmondjr@gmail.com 🤳 +256 701860898 +256 777260295 👂 Salaama Iwasa, 256 Kampala

Education

Bachelor of science in computer engineering

Busitema University, Tororo

Covered

Web development

Application development

Machine learning

Simulation and modeling

Artificial intelligence

Uganda Advanced Certificate of **Education**

Crested SS makindye Kampala, Kampala

Uganda Certificate of Education

St. Henry's College Ggangu, Kampala

Primary Leaving Education

Kibiri Church of Uganda, Kampala

Aug 2018 - Dec 2022

Jan 2016 - Nov 2017

Jan 2012 - Nov 2015

Feb 2005 - Oct 2011

Employment

Mobile Developer

Mar 2020 - Jan 2021

Intellectsoft, kampala

- Map and sketch the mobile application design and application.
- Documentation of the source code details
- Debugging and deployment

Recess Trainer

Apr 2021 - Present

Apr 2020 - Present

Busitema University, Tororo

I train

- Device programming
- Web development
- Mobile Development
- Ethical hacking
- Networking
- Artificial intelligence

Application Developer

Self employed, Kampala

I develop personal applications and websites

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.

Python

Arduino Programming

Java

kotlin

Html

CSS

Personal details

Date of birth June 28, 1999

Place of birth

Kampala

Gender

Male

Nationality

Ugandan

Civil status

Unmarried

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/beteiserichmond-619664213

Computer Engineer

Machine Learning engineer

Al Specialist

Skills

Graphics Designer

References

Dr. OWOMUGISHA GODLIVER

BUAIIR, TORORO

0774820997, ogodliver@gmail.com

Mr Ojok Ivan

INTELLECTSOFT, Kampala

0775186939

Mr Mwenyi Joseph

HEAD OF RECESS TRAINING, BUSITEMA UNIVERSITY, Tororo 0772898318, mwenyi3@gmail.com

Dr. MATOVU DAVIS

HEAD OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING DEPARTMENT, BUSITEMA UNIVERSITY,

0703198514, davismatovu@yahoo.com

Achievements

- I have trained Busitema University computer and electrical engineering students in year one for two years now and have passed.
- I have developed projects using arduino solving real life projects

Certificates

Uganda Institute Of Professional	Present
Engineers	

Church Children Teacher, Hannigton Feb 2021 Chapel

Projects Manager, Hannigton Chapel

Hall Chairperson Alexander Chinadze Aug 2020

Hall, Busitema University

Campus Speaker, Faculty Of Engineering Mar 2022

Busitema University

Computer Engineering Class Present

Representative (2018/22)

Artificial intelligence

MySql

php

Ethical Hacking

Languages

English

Luganda

Hobbies

- Reading
- Coding

Qualities

- Hard working
- Can Work in groups

Profile

From the moment I produced "Hello world" in the console of my first application in my first year at campus, I knew I was hooked into the world of computers. Computer engineering has never been "just a course" for me, its offered an engaging challenge to continually learn and improve my knowledge and skills in creating applications. What started as a simple "hello world" has become a full-fledged passion that only gets more exciting as I continue learning and coming up with different stuff everyday. I am curently pursuing a Bachelors degree of Science in Computer Engineering at Busitema University who has a vigour to continue learning each and every single day to become better at what am doing.

Internships

Artificial intelligence Internee

Mar 2022 - Apr 2022

BUSITEMA UNIVERSITY ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AND INTERDISCIPLINARY RESEARCH, Tororo

Extracurricular activities

Chess Arbiter and player

Nov 2018 - Present

Busitema University, Tororo